mymusictools.com 2017-08-15

# Free Download Privacy Policy - Privacy Policy

## Introduction

This Privacy Policy discloses how MyMusicTools.com ("we") collects and uses information about visitors of mymusictools.com ("you"). It applies to any person or organization that visit mymusictools.com or use our services. Using our services means that you agree with this Privacy Policy.

## Services We Offer

MyMusicTools.com is a big download archive that aggregates multimedia-related software on a single site. Programs listed on the site are selected manually by us. We test compatibility of the listed software with various operating systems and check it for viruses. Results of these checks may be displayed as logos on the corresponding program's page. We also write product descriptions, reviews and tutorials, describing features and showing usage examples for the programs represented on our site.

We list both free and paid (shareware) software on our site.

On pages of MyMusicTools.com and when you download software from our site, various advertising offers may be displayed. These offers are provided by third parties and are subject to their privacy policies and terms of use.

## Information We Collect

We may collect impersonal information supplied by your browser and system when you connect to our server. This information may include: your IP address, operating system and its version, preferred languages, screen resolution, browser name and type, pages that you visit and downloads that you start on our site. We do not use cookies to track visitors. We do not collect any other information if you click on ads or install a program from our site.

If you contact us using the contact forms available on the site, we may keep all messages we receive from your and we sent in reply along with your email address, name, and other information you provide about yourself.

Information collected by the programs represented on our site is subject to privacy policies and terms of use of the corresponding developers / owners of the programs.

## How The Collected Information Is Used

We use the collected information in statistical analysis with the purpose of improving and optimizing our services. When you contact us using a contact form on our site, we use your email address and other information you provide solely for the purpose of replying to your request.

## Sharing The Collected Information

As described above, most information we collect is anonymous (screen resolution, operating system version, etc.). We do not share any information we receive about yourself or your system with any person or organization. We do not share your name, email address or other information provided by you on our contact form.

## Changes

We reserve the right to review, update or change this Privacy Policy. The latest revision of the Privacy Policy can always be found in the "Privacy Policy" section of our site. The page you are reading contains the latest revision of our Privacy Policy.
